masalatime.com 2014-04-06

# Masala Time — Jokes, videos, humor, games and funny pictures!

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**  
Masala Time Interactive has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. This document discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site. 

* * *

**Information Automatically Logged**   
The IP address, browser details, OS etc are logged into the system to gather broad demographic information to configure the website to provide the best services to you. 

No personal or confidential information is collected automatically. 

**Cookies**   
Cookies are used on Masala Time to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly to ensure a better surfing experience. The information in the cookies is specifically handled by external advertising agencies who serve the ads that you see on the website. 

No personal or confidential information is collected automatically. 

**Mailing Lists**   
You can subscribe to the Masala Time mailing lists (standard 'Jokes and 'Non-veg Jokes' version) by entering your email id and other details in the given fields. 

We generally send weekly or monthly emails that contain jokes and other fun stuff. Please note that the 'Non-Veg Jokes' version is meant for persons above the age of 18 years. Mailers to persons below that age will not be sent out. 

At any point of time you can go to the subscription page and unsubscribe from this list and will thereafter receive no emails from us. 

Your email address and other details are not shared with any company or organisation. Basis your subscription with Masala Time you shall recieve mails only from Masala Time. 

**Registered Members**   
Members of the Masala Club get to participate in contests, games and discussion forums. We require the registered users to provide details like name, age and address to access these features of the website. All of this information is kept completely confidential.

Contact information is used to configure and provide better content to our visitors. The mailing address is used to send prizes to winners. Your email is kept strictly confidential unless otherwise indicated on the contest forms. Occasionally, participants might receive information from Masala Time on new contests that happen on Masala Time and similar updates. 

**External Links**   
This site contains links to other sites. Masala Time is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any websites whose links are provided on this website or those which link to us. 

**Public Forums**   
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

When you use our 'Tell a Friend' feature to inform your friends about this site, the email address of the sender and receipient is recorded by us. This is done to protect all internet users' interest in the process of preventing abuse & curbing spam. These email addresses are not used in any mailing lists or any form of spam. 

**Children's Guidelines**   
We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.
  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent
  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:
    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.
    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.
    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.
  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service.
  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.
  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.
  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children.
  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online.

**Contacting the Web Site**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact the Webmaster.
